Lyrics, Composition, Arrangement by Miku Hatsune
Here we go! This time I will be talking with Ruru Danbara of JuiceJuice and Nanami Kubota of Ocha no Oma.
This is a program that takes you behind the scenes of the production of various artists belonging to the upfront group.
We will show you the process of recording and rehearsal.
Now then, let's start with a behind-the-scenes look at the two MCs.
I, Lanbala, have been trying to perform with a focus on dance since the start of the tour.
JuiceJuice's choreography and the songs themselves are the same, but there are many mature and feminine choreographies,
I try to perform with a little bend in my body and neck, rather than standing in a straight line,
It is like she is hiding behind the monitor, or she is curving her body a little bit.
For example, those who cannot hear this video have various impressions. But I want to talk about this video with my ears, so please let me know what you recommend.
I try to perform with curves in mind as I explore how it would look better if it looked like this instead of like this when it's projected on me.
I'm going around the tour now, thinking that I would like to show my performance in a curvy way.
I love the flexibility of Dambada's dance.
I also like the sound framing.
But there is one dance that I like.
The first choreography of "Pocky Music" is very curvy.
I like it because it's a very feminine music dance.
I often said to Mr. Dambada when we were performing.
I think it's cool.
I'm glad you could feel my curves.
Yes, I, Kubota...
I'm Kubota, and we've just started our 47 prefectures tour.
We'll be touring at a live house, so we'll be very close to everyone.
I'm very close to you all, so I can really feel your energy.
I can really feel the energy of the audience.
I feel like I'm creating the live show together with you all.
I'm having a lot of fun!
I'm really looking forward to buying souvenirs for each of the 47 prefectures
I'm really looking forward to buying souvenirs for myself.
I always try to buy at least one souvenir at the local parks so that I can bring it back home. I'm always ready to buy one souvenir to take home from a local park or something.
I have a goal.
Hiroshima
I love Hiroshima-yaki so much that I would like to go there for it.
I think it's good to go to a caterer because of course it's delicious, but it's even hotter and tastier when it's interesting.
The first thing I'd like to share with you is the making of the music video for Morning Musume。 23's latest single "Sukkoku Fever".
Please take a look at the making of the music video for Morning Musume 23's newest single, "Sukkoukou Fever.
Please, please, please.
Please.
Good morning!
This is Morning Musume。 s METAL 3
I'm Morning Musume's METAL 3.
Today, we're going to sing a dance song.
It's going to be a dance song.
quite a lot.
When we have this system
We'll do it in block blocks.
There are of course some places where we don't take
in cranes where this system has changed completely.
This time
that we are going to do a solid dance in terms of physique.
The timing is called
Music
Yes, complete
OK
Yes, sir
Yes, sir.
Yes, sir.Yes, sir.
Yes, OK
Okay. Okay.
Okay, I'm coming through.
Yes, sir.
Thank you.
The music video shoot has begun.
The set is so beautiful.
It's like nothing I've ever seen before.
Sparkling.
There are all kinds of decorations.
It's my favorite at this point.
The camera moves up and down.
The members are having a lot of fun filming.
We're having a lot of fun taking pictures.
I'll be taking many more pictures after this.
I hope you all enjoy watching it.
Three
Re-moment
Birthday is here.
Try to have fun!
Let's go!
Yes!
This will be Fukumura-san's last music video shoot.
but it's like he's supposed to make you smile.
I'm sure it will end without making you feel sad.
The music video is moving at a snail's pace.
I felt that time is precious.Because time felt precious.
I'll do my best for the day.
Well then, thank you for watching!
Thank you for watching!
Great, great, great.
That one person's consciousness can change the times.
As for the point of the dance...
The point of the dance is that it's a little bit sexy and it's a little bit fun.
I think the point of the dance is that it's a little bit sexy, and it's a little bit fun to dance together.
I think that's the point of this show.
The teacher told us that it's not so much that we have to be all dressed up, but rather
I think we should dance in a way that reminds everyone of a mirror ball
I think it would be good if we dance in a way that reminds people of the mirror ball that we all enjoy.
I think that's what we should focus on.
Yes, sir.
BREAK FIRE! WENESSA JOB!
Have more fun!
Shine brighter than anything else
Tonight you're an angel
You'll make everyone happy
Woo...
You're an angel
You'll make everyone happy
Woo...
You're an angel
You'll make everyone happy
Woo...
You're an angel You're an angel.
...you're an angel.
You're an angel.
You're an angel
Congratulations!
Music video shooting has been completed.
Thank you very much.
I had a surprise for you at the last shoot,
I received flowers.
Congratulations.
Do you have time to finish?
No, I don't.
How many shots did you take?
The first 45, right?
Now it's 73.
There is more than one music video per CD, isn't there?
That's how much history is packed into a CD,
You can feel how big the flowers are.
It's huge, isn't it?
It's really big.
It's amazing, isn't it?
Everyone brought them,
It was amazing.
The staff members were standing on my shoulders,
I was about to give them flowers.
I was like, "What am I going to do?
It's not often that I'm the one who wants to give flowers during a music video.
That's right.
So I told them to keep the camera rolling, I asked him to please keep the camera rolling,
I asked him to turn the camera around twice,
I asked him to do that.
So that's how it happened.
Then it came out a little.
But I was surprised.
Is it really, you know, a world record?
Cloud.
What?
Come on, man.
It's over, it's over, it's over.
I had a hand, but I'm glad I got it. I thought I got a good look at him when I gave it to him.
It was really fun, and I thought, "This is the last one, and I have no regrets.
We did our best so that many people would listen to our 73rd single, so please watch it a lot.
Please look at it a lot.
Mizuki Tomita's graduation single, but I thought the song was very bright and happy,
The way it was shot was amazing.
The way it was shot was amazing. It was very different. There were clay shapes that I had never seen before going around on top of each other, or going very close to each other,
It was an interesting behind-the-scenes experience, with so many different ways of filming.
I thought it was really cool to see all these people dancing so crisply on the jacket.
When I listened to the song, I thought it was a great song because it had a great nuance like a man's true face in the A melody and the last part of the song.
This is the making of Morning Musume。23、Sutsukkou Fever、Music Video Shooting.
Thank you for your hard work.
Next is JuiceJuice Romance no Tochu 2023 JUICEJUICE Ver. Instrumental Recording
Here is the recording of JuiceJuice's newest album "2023 JUICEJUICE Ver." which was released on October 11.
I'll try to get it out once, thank you very much.
Please subscribe to our channel.
Please subscribe to our channel!
Thank you for watching!
Please subscribe to our channel! Please subscribe to our channel!
Yes, yes, you know the bass solo at the beginning of the interlude?
After that, there's a cutting solo on the guitar.
I was hoping to get a little more excitement in the latter half of the song, but now I'm not so sure.
But I really like that bass part.
I like that bass, so I'd like to keep it that way, but I'm not sure if I want the heat to go up in the second half.
I'd be happy to have them go like that, but in the second half, I'd be happy to see the heat level go up.
I'm going to go to the next one.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So I think we're going to go for that, too, Eleppi.
Well, let's go one more time.
I'm looking forward to it.
Subscribe to our channel
Please subscribe to our channel.
Well, I don't think we're going to go far with this base.
What do you think? What do you think?
Well, if there's anything you guys can do...
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Let's do it.
That second Bm and then the next Am.
Oh, okay.
Two shots, please.
Please.
The second Bm and then the next Am.Bm's second shot and up to the next Am.
Thank you very much for your hard work!
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Thank you very much.
I'm just wondering if there are any odd names for the door balls, etc.
I was just wondering if it might be up there.
Oh!
I don't know.
I don't know, but if we go that far...
I wonder if they will be covered by the blast.
Yes, it will.
The first one on top...
That's possible.
Always.
That might be a good idea.
Let me see if I can do this.
Yes, please.
Yes, it's a matchy.
Could you please give us the four bars of the first B?
Yes, sir.
Also, please let me do the whole ending.
YOKARIKARI.
Yes, sir.
YOKARI: Yes.
Yes.
Yes, I'll do it.
Please subscribe to our channel.
I think that's great.
Okay, well, I'd like to hear what you guys have to say.
Please subscribe to our channel.Please subscribe to our channel!
katchoey
I think it's good.
Thank you very much.
In the middle of romance, we re-recorded the soundtrack with live sound.
The vocals were also re-recorded with the current members.
I was so overwhelmed by the greatness of it.
I was overwhelmed by how amazing it was, and then I saw you play it again.
I was overwhelmed by the greatness of the music, but when I saw them playing again, I realized that they played Juice Juice's songs for us.
I could really feel it.
But even at the concert
I could really feel the live sound.
I can get into the groove with the fans who are watching us.
And the fans who are watching us
And we can also get into a groove and dance to it.
I want you to hear more and more of the new sound
I want you to listen to it more and more.
We also wanted to listen to it a lot more.
I've never seen you play the instruments in the middle of "Romance" before.
Everyone's hands were moving so fast.
I really felt that the song was made by building up all these individual sounds.
I could hear sounds that I wouldn't normally hear if I was just listening.
I thought it was really wonderful.
That's all for JuiceJuice, in the middle of romance.
2023JuiceJuice Ver. Instrumental Recording
Fifteen years ago, this country was divided into West and East by the Tokyo Tower due to the war.
We recommend this color dress for the color change.
I think it would be suitable for the four-letter priest.
Yes, as you said, I will have them carried in an attache case. Yes, I will have them carried in an attache case, as you said.
What's it really like?
Working style, time off, etc.?
Welcome. What can I get you?
An ice-cream convection.
Yes, sir.
This is where we're meeting?
Yeah, the four guys over there seem to be carrying an attaché case just like this one.
How did you guess that attaché case?
Yes, sir. I'm all set.
Bin Wan manager Ichijo, who will be my best friend.
I'm Reina Ichiroka, playing Ichijo.
Yes, I'm Yuha Yamatsuki, Mr. Show.
Bye bye.
Well, for BEYOND, this stage is the most challenging one for me, even though I've played the leading roles many times,
I think this is the most challenging stage for me.
Not only singing and dancing, but also action, and we are going to try our hand at magic.
I play Mr. Show, the magician, and Ichijo is the manager.
Yes, I'm the manager. We have been training together for a long time.
They are my friends.
Everyone is so cool.
They are really cool.
Really.
Each and every one of them is really, I don't know.
I don't know,
We didn't see the action in rehearsal, so we didn't know what to expect.
I saw it for the first time when they actually performed it through, and it was very cool.
I really want people to see it. I would like many people to see our Beyoncé group's efforts. As a matter of fact, I am doing the same.
Thank you very much for telling me that the tickets for the Tokyo show have been sold out.
But, you know, it looks like you can still get tickets for the Osaka show, so there is still a chance, everyone. I hope you will come to Osaka as well. But, you know, it looks like we can still get tickets for the Osaka show, so there is still a chance, folks. We hope you will come to Osaka, too.
We are waiting for you. I'll do my best.
Don't worry, we'll manage somehow.
Let's start with the A melody, "It's so sad, isn't it?
It's so sad.
Two lines.
And then we'll sing until the next line, "Oh, I'm so sad.
Oh, until...
So, overall, the image is rather refreshing.
And you sing it in a rather bouncy way.
Bouncing, yes.
Music
Photographs from last year. We laughed about how young we were.
We both act like adults, but it's still sad.
I can get a little more rhythm out of the last verse.
But it's so sad.
It's all kind of connected right now.
It's starting to sound like "but-setsu.
I'll make it "but-setsu.
But, but, but, but...
And what's with the accent?
But it's so sad.
But, but, but, but, but, but, but, but, but, but, but, but, but.
I agree. It's like a thrust.
But it's so sad.
But it's sad.
Let's try that.
2. accent
Last year's photoshoot. We laughed about how young we were.
We acted like adults. But it's so sad. You two are all grown up now, but it's so sad.
Yeah, I'm feeling good now.
Let's try the second half.
Let's do the second half.
Matching angled pieces... dazzling memories... a sign of how far we've come.
Yeah, it's like a rhythm.
Yeah.
Matching angle piece piece piece
Memories are dazzling A little tighter on the back
Memories are dazzling in the glide of the far-off example
I heard you've come a long way
I'll put a there a there a there a there
You heard that?
And the "testimony" is a little more firm.
Proof.
And then drop the "testimony" at the end.
Yeah, like a little bit of a throw.
I want to cross it with the next set.
So it's a little bit long on purpose.
Proof, right?
Yeah, something like that.
Cross with the next set.
Matching angle pieces The memories are dazzling
It's proof that we've come a long way
OK, OK, B melody, let's go!
Freshly grated energy, too big future are you ready
Before you overthink it, that's not it, don't be no lady
A little more lighthearted A little lighter
The future is you ready
I'll try not to use katakana there, too.
are you ready
Sounds a bit English, doesn't it?
Don't overthink it before you overthink it
Don't cut too much
Let's get into the groove, but don't just cut it off.
Hey, that's it... can be a little cute.
That's it!
Well, let's make it fresh.
I hope it's a bit wordy
Fresh energy, too low future Are you ready?
Before you overthink it, right?
That's it, isn't it? I'll just take that.
Let's be a little cute.
So long. It's like a heart.
I'm going to sing it as if I'm saying it as a line. I'll sing it like I'm saying it with words.
Okay, then.
OK, I understand.
Okay, let's go to the chorus.
Don't be afraid, it's my life, the end point can be anything
We're each going to make it happen with love
Don't be afraid, there's no hesitation, let's do it
Still, I'll be waiting for you someday, for your hesitation
Courage, it's my life
Yes, sir
Jump on board It's my life, it doesn't matter what the end point is
We each bring our love and go to make it come true
Don't worry, there's no hesitation It's okay. I'm not hesitating.
Let's do it.
Still someday wait for the lost
Courage It's my life
I felt the passion grow stronger as the A melody, B melody, and chorus lead into the chorus, and I talked with the director about how to accentuate the melody.
I talked with the director about how to accentuate the melody, and I thought it turned out to be a very nice song.
I had a strong image of blue and freshness in the music video, so when I saw the recording video, I was really excited and passionate.
But when I saw the recording video, I was impressed by how passionately she sings the song.
I had an image of her singing in a fresh, smooth, and smiling manner, so it was impressive to see Marin-chan singing so passionately.
This was the vocal recording of Tsubaki Factory's "Yuki It's my life" by Marin Fukuda.
I want to have the strength to accept the weakness that I believed I should have
I want to get the strength to accept it
I'll live apart from you, that's all, I'll be fine.
I love autumn. What do you like?
Danbarrel Lutte! It's time for Nanami Kubota to say goodbye to Apkami! We've seen a lot of footage this time, but I, Kubota, would like to share with you a behind-the-scenes look at the filming of Morning Musume 23's amazing heaver music video.
I've never seen the camera rolling so fast behind the scenes of Morning Musume・23's amazing Heaver music video, so I was really impressed by the way they did it.
I had never seen a camera rolling like that before, so it was really fun to see how they made that amazing music video.
I Dambara is in the middle of romance 2023 Juice Juice version of the instruments was really cool and the recording was really cool.
I was shocked to see that you were able to take all of the pictures at once and make it all into a full-length video.
It's over so quickly, so please watch it again.
I can't wait to see it again!
UpCami takes you behind the scenes of the production of various artists belonging to the UpFront Group.
Please subscribe to our channel and we'll introduce you to things you don't normally get to see.
This time, UpCami is joined by Danbaralulu of Juice Juice and Nana Kubota of Ocha no Ma!
and Nanami Kubota of Ocha no Ma!
Good bye!
Next time
The making of the shooting of the music video for "Lonely Bus" by Yoshikazu Miyamoto
And
Morning Musume。23 Sukkoku Fever recording session!Morning Musume。23 Sukkoku Fever Recording will be available soon!
Enjoy!
Thank you for watching!
enjoy!